Hello everyone! I'm Houda Khiati, a passionate full-stack developer,
currently doing my work-study program at Equativ. If you're looking for someone who brings both
technical expertise and a sharp sense of real-world impact, you're in the right place.
I'm in my final year at Institut Galilée – Université Sorbonne Paris Nord, and my journey
so far has allowed me to gain a rare combination of technical and functional skills.
Let me give you a few concrete examples. At Lafarge Holcim,
I developed a web application using Angular and SpringBoot to manage access and
real-time attendance — a direct impact, immediate results. At Marjane Holding,
I dove into data analysis with R and Power BI, helping to
optimize store layout based on real customer behavior.
Now at Equativ, I'm focused on internal tools — making workflows smarter,
improving user experience, and ensuring data reliability at every
step. What drives me? I thrive in dynamic, human environments, where
technology truly serves continuous improvement. Collaboration, inclusion, and real
social or environmental impact aren't just buzzwords for me — they're core values.
I speak French, English, and Arabic, and I'm always eager to learn, create meaningful solutions,
and bring my energy to a team with purpose.
Thank you for listening — and if this resonates with you, feel free to reach out!